https://projectmanager.com.au/terms-conditions/

Skip to content
Advertisers and contributors to ProjectManager.com.au acknowledge they are aware of the provisions of the Anti-Discrimination Act 1977 and the Trade Practices Act 1974 in relation to false and misleading advertising or statements under other unfair practices and the penalties for breach of provisions of those Acts. The publisher accepts no responsibility for such breaches.
Opinions expressed by contributors are their own and not necessarily endorsed by ProjectManager.com.au or the publisher. All material on ProjectManager.com.au is copyright and may not be reproduced in whole or in part without the express permission of the publishers.
Privacy Policy
ProjectManager.com.au is committed to maintaining the trust of our readers, visitors and users.
ProjectManager.com.au offers a variety of online resources, and on occasion we may ask you to provide some of your information to assist us in providing additional information or services.
When you register, advertise or subscribe on this site, you will be asked for your personal information. We use the information you provide, which may include name, email address, postcode, so that you can use features on this site including commenting on an
article, subscribing to our newsletter or for any
similar form of
information gathering, including conducting surveys or
entering
competitions.
Please take time to understand how we collect information from you.
Privacy Policy
Special Considerations
ProjectManager.com.au cannot guarantee that the information you provide to us is completely safe, although we practise the utmost care to prevent problems. There may be technical problems beyond our control that may make it accessible to unauthorised persons. There may also be visitors to the site who gather and use information available.
We may revise our privacy policy in the future to adjust to such changes. We advise you to check this privacy statement regularly for changes or updates.
NewsGovernment funding supports better project deliveryDecember 2, 2020Remote workers prefer trust over technologyOctober 12, 2020Flexibility is key to post-COVID work practicesJuly 2, 2020AIPM celebrates 20 years of project excellenceMay 21, 2020Design and Building Practitioners Bill not adequate for projects, says AIPMDecember 9, 2019WhitepapersProject Management and its Barriers—Joelle JelloProject and organisational barriers in the site inspection phase—Amish Trilok JoshiImproving project performance through tacit knowledge sharing—Katja SinningLearning styles in today’s business domain—Nick Dominique-BouvatThe importance of effective knowledge management and conversion—Alice ChivellSubmit a whitepaperPages
About us
Advertise
Contact us
Legal
Submit white paper
Terms and conditions
Search for:
